Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Go get Lyudmilla out.
Get dressed. We have to go.
If you chose this life, you have to
be ready to give up everything.
- I'm not.
- Then that makes us even.
It's good we made peace.
You should be aware that I'm not
the only patron Mr Godman has.
Tell your father that his friend,
Veniamin, will be happy to see him.
It was a threat. It was Vadim
telling me it isn't over.
I talked to my friend.
And if he's willing to meet, would
you be prepared to go to Moscow?
In Moscow, they kill you!
GUNFIRE
Natasha!
THEY SPEAK RUSSIAN
Where are you going?
I have to meet someone.
Thank your mother for me.
I'll come and see you in a few days.
Wait over there, please.
Visa.
Phone, please.
Can I make a call first?
- I need to let my family know where...
- Later.
G-O-D-M-A-N.
First name, Alexander.
He was supposed to be on flight 237.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
PHONE VIBRATES
- Yeah?
- He was on the flight.
They don't have any
other information.
Let me know if you hear from him.
I will make some calls here.
Thank you, Joseph.
KEYS RATTLE, LOCK CLICKS
Mr Godman.
I'm not sure what I'm doing here.
I also don't know what you do here.
I had some business meetings.
What business?
Can I speak to someone
from the British Consulate?
She was my god-daughter.
She was 21.
She had nothing to do
with your feud.
Who did you come to see?
- I'd like to speak to a lawyer.
- No lawyers.
No consulate.
Nobody knows you're here.
The people who invited me
to Moscow know that I'm here.
Just tell me
who they are, I'll inform them.
I'm sure they'll find out
for themselves, sooner or later.
If something happened to
Vadim's daughter, I'm sorry.
But I had nothing to do with it.
You have until tonight...
...to tell me who you're here to see.
If you don't...
...you can apologise
to her father yourself.
DOOR SLAMS
Come, please.
Can I ask where I'm being taken?
The airport.
Can I make a phone call?
No phone, no computer.
We give them to your embassy later.
Why are we stopping?
We have time.
Do you have a cigarette, please?
You can smoke in here.
I'm sorry, I don't speak Russian.
It's OK.
Hey, do you speak English?
Real Madrid are going to win
the league this year.
Barcelona win.
We've got Gareth Bale.
Neymar.
- What about Pepe?
- Messi.
TYRES SCREECH
VOICES UPSTAIRS
THEY SHOUT IN RUSSIAN
TRIGGER CLICKS
GATE RATTLES
RATTLING ECHOES
Excuse me, I'm a tourist.
I've lost my phone. Is there...?
MAN SPEAKS RUSSIAN
Hi, do any of you speak English?
A little.
My phone was just stolen.
I need to call a friend.
PHONE VIBRATES
- Hello?
- Papa, I'm in trouble. I need your help.
HE SIGHS
Somewhere near University Square.
You have to get out of Russia.
I've...
...done something.
I ordered a hit on Vadim.
His daughter...
I can't talk now.
I'll call you later.
Oh, thank you.
Your father told me to drive
you to the Ukrainian border.
Not yet.
I don't have a permanent
address right now.
As long as we have a contact
number, that's fine.
Where are you off to so soon?
I didn't know you guys
were coming.
We wanted to surprise you.
- Are you OK? Yeah?
- Yeah. Thank you.
Thanks.
- Good to see you.
- You, too.
You know Antonio, don't you?
No, I don't think so.
Antonio is Alex's friend
from Harvard.
- I'm sorry, Antonio...?
- Mendez.
Your brother has a lot of friends.
- Hi, I'm Femi.
- Hi, Antonio.
Nice meeting you.
- How's Alex?
- I don't know.
He's travelling.
Shall we grab a coffee or something?
No, you must be exhausted.
Does Alex know you're here?
We saw each other a few days ago.
- Well, shall we...?
- Let me know when's a good time to visit.
I'm so happy you're better.
Thank you.
You, too. See you soon.
- Nice to meet you.
- My pleasure.
- Good to meet you.
- See you.
Colonel Federov.
Colonel Federov!
Vadim.
My friend Oleg says you have
a proposition for me.
The people I represent are looking
to do business here.
Given their reputation, it would
have to be a very attractive offer
to justify the risks.
The business I'm talking about
is worth 300 billion a year.
If you'd invested in my
fund at launch, you'd have
doubled your money.
An investment with my associates
would have given you
a 5,000% return
over the same period.
The profit you're talking
about comes at a human cost.
What I'm proposing to do is increase
the profit whilst reducing the cost.
Right now, Vadim Kalyagin smuggles
300,000 kilos of heroin
into this country.
You have two million addicts,
50,000 deaths a year.
His profits are shrinking
whilst the crime rate
associated with them
is rising all the time.
I studied business
at Harvard, like you, Mr Godman.
How is your proposal any different?
My associates are only interested in
using your ports to move
their product into Europe.
In exchange for your protection...
...they would pay you a commission
and guarantee that none of
the product would be sold here.
The commission I'm talking
about could in turn be used to
boost the legal economy,
build hospitals, schools...
...even fight the war on crime.
And what would you do
about Vadim Kalyagin?
He won't deal with my associates.
And my associates,
they won't deal with him.
The mafia culture
he represents is outdated.
His methods are
violent, inefficient,
draws too much attention.
Attention which doesn't
reflect well on this country.
He lets emotion get in the way
of business,
which isn't good for any of us.
Oleg told me you could be humble
when it suited you...
...but ruthless, too.
I haven't always had a choice.
I'll need to discuss this
with my partners.
Of course.
How's Femi?
Patient.
Are you seeing Alex's friend?
Do I look like I'm in
a fit state to see anyone?
Sorry, sorry.
No. Idiot to ask.
He was being helpful and concerned
when I needed it.
I know you can't forgive my brother,
but can I please say something?
He's looked after me my whole life.
My mother and father, too.
He was trying to protect us.
The last thing he wanted was
something to happen to you.
It isn't just what happened, Katya.
I don't think...
...I know who he is any more.
I don't think
he even knows himself.
They're economists, like you.
You'll present your proposal,
go over the numbers,
and then they'll make
their decision.
CAR UNLOCKS
GUNSHOTS
THEY SHOUT IN RUSSIAN
RAPID GUNFIRE
ENGINE STARTS
TYRES SCREECH
We have a lot of factions
and rivalries in this country.
People who do not wish us well.
Right now, we are on top, but it
won't always be that way.
Like I said,
I don't want to ruffle any feathers.
Then we'll meet your associates
and take it from there.
There's one more thing.
The man who shot Vadim's daughter
was arrested last night.
He tried to cut a deal
and implicated your father.
My father was 1,000 miles away.
Of course.
But for the sake of our future
partnership, it would be better
if you distance yourself from him.
Part of the reason I came here was
so that my father could return.
Our rivals could build a case
against him to discredit you.
That would be bad for all of us.
He's been away for
more than 15 years.
All he thinks about are
the mistakes he's made.
He doesn't want to get
back into business.
He just wants to come home.
I'm afraid it's not possible
any more.
I understand.
PHONE VIBRATES
- Hello?
- Ilya.
This isn't what I came here for.
I came here to make a deal.
And you've made your deal.
Now you have to see it through.
Neither of us can afford
to leave Vadim alive.
You don't have to do this yourself.
DOORBELL RINGS
DOOR BUZZES
DOOR SHUTS
Ilya?
Do you like football?
Sometimes.
Do you have a favourite team?
No.
I'm not surprised.
There's a remote control.
You can turn it off.
HE SWITCHES TV OFF
HE GRUNTS
Did Ilya give you a message for me?
No.
Tell him I would do the
same thing for my family.
Your uncle would be so proud of you.
Your father, as well.
You did what they couldn't do.
I'm sorry for what happened
to your daughter.
I didn't know.
You want me to forgive you?
That's the only power
I've got in this world.
So I won't give it up.
How is your fiancee?
She's better.
Good.
You still love her?
I've told you before...
...if you choose this life...
...if you want her to be safe...
...you'll have to give her up.
Your family, too.
Everyone you love.
Everyone.
You'll be alone...
...every single day.
Until someone comes to put
you out of your misery.
My wallet.
There's a picture of my daughter
I would love to have.
HE TAKES A DEEP BREATH
GUNSHOT
Katya told me Alex went to Russia?
He's safe now.
Will you go back, too?
What for? This is our home now.
I love my country, but I don't
belong there any more.
Anyway, the whole world
is the same now.
Gucci here, Gucci there.
I hope we can still see each other.
Even if Alex and I aren't together.
Katya told me about your baby.
Our baby.
You know someone is a part of the
family when you feel their pain.
You're like my daughter now.
And who knows? Dmitri and I argue
every day for 40 years
and I still forgive him.
He's a good boy.
I'm biased, I know.
But he's my son.
When will you come back?
I don't know.
It depends what he wants to do.
Why what he wants?
You can decide, too.
I made you something.
I don't know what is, either.
My colleagues and I have discussed
Mr Godman's proposal
and he has our full confidence.
With your permission,
I'm going to withdraw
and leave our side
of the negotiations to him.
Thanks.
These terms are unacceptable.
Those are our terms.
Your terms?
We sent you here to arrange
an introduction, that's all.
Antonio.
We did you a favour.
Who the hell do you think you are?
Forgive me, Mr Alegre, but it might
be simpler if you and I
discussed these matters alone.
We both speak for our
respective sides.
In return for an open door
and protection for your shipments,
we'd ask for a 50% split
of every consignment.
We would have no involvement in any
business from your other routes,
but we would control
all distribution
that passes through our territory.
50%, it's impossible...
...and we have no interest
in being wholesalers.
Getting your product into Europe is
the hardest part of your business.
The Dutch and Spanish ports you have
used are no longer viable and you
haven't managed to gain a foothold
in West Africa, unlike your rivals.
Through the networks and routes
that I will inherit,
I'll manage the sale
and distribution of your product
in any territories
that don't conflict with your own.
In return, I'd ask that you don't
interfere with my contacts
or encroach on any territory
where I represent you.
I work on your behalf.
I don't work for you.
I don't mean that as
a mark of disrespect.
I simply think it's the best
way for all of us to make money.
PHONE VIBRATES
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org